{
    "id": "b99bfb3fb1ac45ad8e95ee45c202e02d",
    "title": "Auxiliaries Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The boy …………………… playing the piano.",
            "description": "We use is here because the subject is the singular countable noun boy.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f5140226d7f646b3adc4fe7d2aa77497"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………………… sent the parcel.",
            "description": "We use the present perfect to talk about recently finished actions or situations. This verb form is made with has or have.",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "have",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "51fff169ec864ab981ece28fc1bb0665"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ……………………… working since morning.",
            "description": "We make the present perfect continuous tense forms with have been + ing form. ",
            "answers": [
                "be",
                "being",
                "been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "65d1f517e616468da40453f6616a4e3e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Uncle said that he ………………………. come with me.",
            "description": "Would is the past tense of will in reported speech.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "009b0bf73ca440acb41af425cd71b382"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. visit the beach when I was in Mumbai.",
            "description": "We use used to to talk about a past habit.",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "was used to",
                "had used to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "de309ea262b748739404f90c355af518"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………. not go out alone at night.",
            "description": "When dare is used as a modal auxiliary, it does not the take the marker –s.",
            "answers": [
                "dare",
                "dares"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "412f02fe98564960b7ac40a186db080b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………. to speak to me.",
            "description": "When dare is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to. Also, questions and negatives are made with do and does.",
            "answers": [
                "doesn't dare",
                "daren't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "97e04536e6664e899d21c92bc242b909"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………. write to him.",
            "description": "When need is used as a modal auxiliary, questions and negatives are made without do and does.",
            "answers": [
                "need not",
                "don't need",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e76027ab024b40e0bdd2a68223c66950"
        },
        {
            "question": "You don’t need ……………………….. for me.",
            "description": "When need is used as an ordinary verb, it is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "to wait",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ce6090b422e2424da07d064de4b6ad0f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………… have told me before borrowing my car.",
            "description": "We use should to indicate obligation.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1dee3fc0a2f049e7b3de4822a86cc268"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. I carry this bag for you?",
            "description": "Should is used in polite offers of help.",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would",
                "Will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7f1e079b4533443985c131675726fba2"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. you help me with cooking?",
            "description": "Would is used in polite requests for help.",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7ebc18a9ff3f4d3594aa4921fba09d46"
        }
    ]
}